export const questions = [
    {
        "id": 1,
        "category": 1,
        "question": "Who is the most decorated Brazilian football player",
        "answer": "D",
        options : [
          {
            id: '1a',
            label: 'A',
            option: 'Pele'
          },
          {
            id: '1b',
            label: 'B',
            option: 'Neymar'
          },
          {
            id: '1c',
            label: 'C',
            option: 'Oscar'
          },
          {
            id: '1d',
            label: 'D',
            option: 'Dani Alves'
          },
        ]
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "category": 1,
      "question": "In what year did Nigeria win their first Olympic gold medal",
      "answer": "D",
      options : [
        {
          id: '1a',
          label: 'A',
          option: '1993'
        },
        {
          id: '1b',
          label: 'B',
          option: '1960'
        },
        {
          id: '1c',
          label: 'C',
          option: '2002'
        },
        {
          id: '1c',
          label: 'D',
          option: '1996'
        },
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "category": 1,
      "question": "Which famous Nigeria footballer is nicknamed 'The weapon of mass destruction in Italy",
      "answer": "A",
      options : [
        {
          id: '1a',
          label: 'A',
          option: 'Obafemi Martins'
        },
        {
          id: '1b',
          label: 'B',
          option: 'Victor Anichebe'
        },
        {
          id: '1c',
          label: 'C',
          option: 'Gabriel Agbonlahor'
        },
        {
          id: '1d',
          label: 'D',
          option: 'Taye Taiwo'
        },
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "category":1,
      "question": "In what year did wayne Rooney score a hat-rick on his Manchester United debut",
      "answer": "D",
      options : [
        {
          id: '1a',
          label: 'A',
          option: '2005'
        },
        {
          id: '1b',
          label: 'B',
          option: '2003'
        },
        {
          id: '1c',
          label: 'C',
          option: '2009'
        },
        {
          id: '1d',
          label: 'D',
          option: '2004'
        },
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "category": 1,
      "question": "Where is The famous Maracana stadium located",
      "answer": "B",
      options : [
        {
          id: '1a',
          label: 'A',
          option: 'Nigeria'
        },
        {
          id: '1b',
          label: 'B',
          option: 'Brazil'
        },
        {
          id: '1c',
          label: 'C',
          option: 'Spain'
        },
        {
          id: '1d',
          label: 'D',
          option: 'Mexico'
        },
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "category": 1,
      "question": "What is the full name of manchester united legend, Nani",
      "answer": "A",
      options : [
        {
          id: '1a',
          label: 'A',
          option: 'Loius Almeda Da Cunha'
        },
        {
          id: '1b',
          label: 'B',
          option: 'Loius Nani'
        },
        {
          id: '1c',
          label: 'C',
          option: 'OKonta Okeke'
        },
        {
          id: '1d',
          label: 'D',
          option: 'Alvaro Cadriozo'
        },
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "category": 1,
      "question": "Which of these players has reprsented two national teams",
      "answer": "C",
      options : [
        {
          id: '1a',
          label: 'A',
          option: 'luis Figo'
        },
        {
          id: '1b',
          label: 'B',
          option: 'Javier Zanetti'
        },
        {
          id: '1c',
          label: 'C',
          option: 'Florent Mlaouda'
        },
        {
          id: '1d',
          label: 'D',
          option: 'Ricardo Kaka'
        },
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "category": 1,
      "question": "Whic of these player wa dubbed the 'new messi' ",
      "answer": "A",
      options : [
        {
          id: '1a',
          label: 'A',
          option: 'Halilovic'
        },
        {
          id: '1b',
          label: 'B',
          option: 'Ricardo Kaka'
        },
        {
          id: '1c',
          label: 'C',
          option: 'Ibrahim Affelay'
        },
        {
          id: '1d',
          label: 'D',
          option: 'Angel Gomez'
        },
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "category": 1,
      "question": "In which year did Kosovo play their first competitve competition",
      "answer": "B",
      options : [
        {
          id: '1a',
          label: 'A',
          option: '2002'
        },
        {
          id: '1b',
          label: 'B',
          option: '2018'
        },
        {
          id: '1c',
          label: 'C',
          option: '2019'
        },
        {
          id: '1d',
          label: 'D',
          option: '1990'
        },
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "category": 1,
      "question": "Whic club did Ferenc Puskas play for",
      "answer": "D",
      options : [
        {
          id: '1a',
          label: 'A',
          option: 'Bayern Munich'
        },
        {
          id: '1b',
          label: 'B',
          option: 'Benfica'
        },
        {
          id: '1c',
          label: 'C',
          option: 'Real Zaragoza'
        },
        {
          id: '1d',
          label: 'D',
          option: 'Real Madrid'
        },
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "category": 1,
      "question": "'Remontada' is associated to what",
      "answer": "A",
      options : [
        {
          id: '1a',
          label: 'A',
          option: 'A comeback'
        },
        {
          id: '1b',
          label: 'B',
          option: 'A defeat'
        },
        {
          id: '1c',
          label: 'C',
          option: 'A victory'
        },
        {
          id: '1d',
          label: 'D',
          option: 'A fixed match'
        },
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "category": 1,
      "question": "How many major trophies did Iniesta win",
      "answer": "B",
      options : [
        {
          id: '1a',
          label: 'A',
          option: '32'
        },
        {
          id: '1b',
          label: 'B',
          option: '37'
        },
        {
          id: '1c',
          label: 'C',
          option: '42'
        },
        {
          id: '1d',
          label: 'D',
          option: '22'
        },
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 13,
      "category": 1,
      "question": "Which of these players never got a red card in their career",
      "answer": "C",
      options : [
        {
          id: '1a',
          label: 'A',
          option: 'Alex Vidal'
        },
        {
          id: '1b',
          label: 'B',
          option: 'Brown Ideye'
        },
        {
          id: '1c',
          label: 'C',
          option: 'Philip Lahm'
        },
        {
          id: '1d',
          label: 'D',
          option: 'Arturo Vidal'
        },
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 14,
      "category": 1,
      "question": "Which club did Manchester United sign Bebe from",
      "answer": "B",
      options : [
        {
          id: '1a',
          label: 'A',
          option: 'Benfica'
        },
        {
          id: '1b',
          label: 'B',
          option: 'Sporting Lisbon'
        },
        {
          id: '1c',
          label: 'C',
          option: 'Braga'
        },
        {
          id: '1d',
          label: 'D',
          option: 'FC Porto'
        },
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 15,
      "category": 1,
      "question": "Who won the inaugral Europa league player of the tournament award",
      "answer": "B",
      options : [
        {
          id: '1a',
          label: 'A',
          option: 'John Oshea'
        },
        {
          id: '1b',
          label: 'B',
          option: 'Paul Labile Pogba'
        },
        {
          id: '1c',
          label: 'C',
          option: 'Evar Banega'
        },
        {
          id: '1d',
          label: 'D',
          option: 'Cristiano Ronaldo'
        },
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 16,
      "category": 1,
      "question": "Who was the secretary General of FIFA when South Afria Hosted the world cup",
      "answer": "D",
      options : [
        {
          id: '1a',
          label: 'A',
          option: 'Micahel Platini'
        },
        {
          id: '1b',
          label: 'B',
          option: 'Alex Ferguson'
        },
        {
          id: '1c',
          label: 'C',
          option: 'Sepp Blatter'
        },
        {
          id: '1d',
          label: 'D',
          option: 'Jerome Valcke'
        },
      ]
    },
]